{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Where was Gol D. Roger born?",
      "answer": "East Blue"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who drew the first Jolly Roger of the Strawhat Pirates?",
      "answer": "Usopp"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the rank of Morgan?",
      "answer": "Captain"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who gave Genzo his scars?",
      "answer": "Arlong"
    },
    {
      "question": "Usopp is from which island?",
      "answer": "Syrup Village"
    },
    {
      "question": "What brand of cigarette does Sanji smoke?",
      "answer": "King Ground"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was sick in their introduction, Johnny or Yosaku?",
      "answer": "Yosaku"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who damaged Luffy's straw hat?",
      "answer": "Buggy"
    },
    {
      "question": "How much Beli did Zoro loan from Nami in Loguetown?",
      "answer": "100,000 Beli"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many confirmed devil fruit users were shown before entering the Grand Line?",
      "answer": "Four"
    },
    {
      "question": "What weapon did Crocus use?",
      "answer": "Harpoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who do we see together with Vivi?",
      "answer": "Mr. 9"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does Mr. 5 fling at his opponents?",
      "answer": "Boogers"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these characters are Logia users?",
      "answer": "Crocodile, Enel"
    },
    {
      "question": "How old is Dr. Kureha pre-timeskip?",
      "answer": "139"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many forms does Chopper have with one Rumble Ball pre-timeskip?",
      "answer": "Seven"
    },
    {
      "question": "When Mr. 2 was on the Going Merry, who did he not touch?",
      "answer": "Sanji"
    },
    {
      "question": "Matsuge initially let two people ride his back, who were they?",
      "answer": "Nami & Chopper"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Luffy’s brother?",
      "answer": "Ace"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Nico Robin’s Devil Fruit ability?",
      "answer": "Hana Hana no Mi"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the shipwright of the Straw Hat Pirates?",
      "answer": "Franky"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the archaeologist of the Straw Hat Pirates?",
      "answer": "Nico Robin"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the musician of the Straw Hat Pirates?",
      "answer": "Brook"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the helmsman of the Straw Hat Pirates?",
      "answer": "Jinbei"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is known as the “Pirate Hunter”?",
      "answer": "Zoro"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the doctor of the Straw Hat Pirates?",
      "answer": "Chopper"
    }
  ]
}
